buyrealfansandlikes.com 2012-02-04

# Privacy Policy | Buy Facebook Fans and Likes

##  Privacy Policy 

We at BuyRealFansandLikes.Com believe strongly in confidentiality. Our site requires certain secure and confidential information from you so we can do our job correctly. This information may be something like: Name, Email Address and Facebook Page.

However, all of this information is held in the strictest form of confidence and is never sold, or given to other service providers or advertisers. The information you provide is used for the sole and express use of completing your service, and is not shared in any way with outside sources or parties.

The only data that is shared is composite traffic data. But this data excludes the use of email addresses or personal information. For instance, we may tell an advertiser that an X number of individuals visit the site, or that Y number of men and Z numbers of women has used the site. But personal information will never be disclosed.

Although we assure you that we do not share your information with anyone, Google does use cookies to serve ads on our sites, and these cookies enable its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to the site. A user may opt out of these cookies by going to the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy and discontinuing the option.

Our company uses the appropriate managerial, electronic, and physical procedures to safeguard all personal information. If you want us to send you your personal identifiable information please send us an e-mail at support@buyrealfansandlikes.com. If any of this personal information is incorrect you can send a request detailing the error to the said email address. To protect our customer’s security and privacy we will verify your identity before making necessary corrections. Any other questions you may have can be directed to support@buyrealfansandlikes.com.
